[

](https://www.agechecked.com/ "AgeChecked")

Our Website Privacy Policy
==========================

**This policy refers to how we safeguard the privacy of our website visitors. For information on how we safeguard the privacy of the users of our age checking services, please scroll down to the ‘Our Privacy Statement’ section below.** 

**SITE PRIVACY POLICY**

AgeChecked Limited (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the [http://www.AgeChecked.com](https://www.agechecked.com/ "https://www.agechecked.com/") website (the “Service”).

We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors.

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information when you use our Website. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

Unless otherwise defined in this Site Privacy Policy, terms used in this Site Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible at [http://www.AgeChecked.com](https://www.agechecked.com/ "https://www.agechecked.com/")

**INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE**

While using our Website and when making an enquiry, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to, your name (“Personal Information”). This information will not be shared with any organisation, other than an organisation that provides email or messaging services and for the sole purpose of us contacting you.

**COOKIES**

We use cookies on our website for optimising the user experience.  We will ask you to consent to our use of cookies when you first visit our website.

**SERVICE PROVIDERS**

We may employ third party companies and individuals to assist in providing the Website, to perform services related to providing the Website, or to assist us in analyzing how our Website is used. We do not share your Personal Information with these third parties.

**LINKS TO OTHER SITES**

Our Website may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit. We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third-party sites or services.

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

We may update our Site Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Site Privacy Policy on this page.

You are advised to review this Site Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Site Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page. If you have any questions about this Site Privacy Policy, please [contact us](mailto:info@agechecked.com "mailto:info@agechecked.com").

**Our Services Privacy Policy**

**This statement refers to how we safeguard the privacy of the users of our age checking services. For information on how we safeguard the privacy of visitors to our website,** [**agechecked.com**](https://www.agechecked.com/ "https://www.agechecked.com/")**, please scroll up to the ‘Our Website Privacy Policy’ section above.** 

**PRIVACY STATEMENT**

AgeChecked Ltd (“us”, “we”, or “our”) provides a service (the “Service”) to organisations to check on the suitability of their customers to access age-restricted products or services.

We take your privacy extremely seriously. This statement informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Identifiable Information (“Your Information”) when you use our Service.

We constantly strive to minimise the requirement for our users to disclose personal information. It is possible to use our Service without disclosing Your Information in some instances. However, in order to meet the requirements of regulators, it is sometimes necessary for us to process Your Information to provide the Service.

We will not use or share Your Information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Statement. We do not use Your Information for any other reason other than to provide the Service. We do not retain Personal Identifiable Information, only anonymised data.

Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Statement, terms used in this Privacy Statement have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible on our website [https://www.agechecked.com.](https://www.agechecked.com./ "https://www.agechecked.com./")

**INFORMATION COLLECTION USE AND STORAGE**

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with Your Information in an iframe/web portal that is hosted securely by us. This information can be used to check your suitability to access age-restricted products or services (“Age Checking”) and send your account information. We do not share Your Information with third parties for any purpose other than Age Checking. We do not share Your Information with the organisation that has asked us to provide this Age Checking Service for them (“Website Operator”).

A Website Operator may send us Your Information and ask us to Age Check you using that information. We may return the results of the Age Check to the Website Operator, but we will not send Your Information to the Website Operator.  
For clarity, a Website Operator will only receive data from us so that they may ascertain your suitability to access the age-restricted service, and not Your Information itself.

Information that we may collect on you, and use to ascertain your suitability to access the age-restricted service could be:

* Your name
    
* Your date of birth or age
    
* Your telephone number
    
* Your address
    
* Your email address
    
* Your IP address
    
* Your payment card information
    
* Information derived from Government issued documentation
    
* Politically exposed persons (PEPs), sanctions and exclusions data

Once an age check has taken place any of Your Information that may have been gathered during the age checking process is removed from our system, apart from:

* Your date of birth or age
    
* Politically exposed persons (PEPs), sanctions and exclusions data (if applicable).

Thus, the information that remains is anonymised and used to ascertain your suitability to access age-restricted services.

**CREATED DATA**

We create data to enable our users to anonymously verify their age without having to disclose their identity via anonymised accounts. We maintain these accounts for client compliance purposes and other valid purposes.

Anonymised accounts can be deactivated at any time by a user through the user portal.

**SERVICE PROVIDERS**

We may employ the following third-party companies to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analysing how our Service is used:

**TRANSFER OF DATA OVERSEAS**

No personal data is transferred from the UK or EU to a Third Country which is either outside of the UK or EU or deemed not to meet the adequate standards of protection for personal data.

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT**

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Statement on this page.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Statement are effective when they are posted on this page.

**CONTACT US**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, please contact us at [dc@agechecked.com](mailto:dc@agechecked.com "mailto:dc@agechecked.com").

CONTACT

* AGECHECKED LTD
* 161-165 Farringdon Road, London, EC1R 3AL.

USEFUL LINKS

SOCIAL

ISO27001 CERTIFICATION

AgeChecked Ltd. is registered in the UK, company number 10016216. © 2022 AgeChecked.

Please enable JavaScript in your browser to complete this form.

1Konto

2Benutzerdaten

3Bankdatan

Vorname

Nachname

GeburtsdatumMM123456789101112/DD12345678910111213141516171819202122232425262728293031/YYYY202420232022202120202019201820172016201520142013201220112010200920082007200620052004200320022001200019991998199719961995199419931992199119901989198819871986198519841983198219811980197919781977197619751974197319721971197019691968196719661965196419631962196119601959195819571956195519541953195219511950194919481947194619451944194319421941194019391938193719361935193419331932193119301929192819271926192519241923192219211920

Adresse

Postleitzahl

Bestätigen

E-Mail-Adresse \*

Passwort \*

* Mind. 8 Zeichen
* Großbuchstaben
* Kleinbuchstaben
* Zahlen

Handynummer (Optional)

BisherigeBestätigen

Bitte geben Sie unten Ihre Bankdaten ein. Um Sie zu authentifizieren, leisten wir eine kleine Einzahlung mit einem eindeutigen Referenzcode auf Ihr Bankkonto. Bitte überprüfen Sie Ihre Bank auf diesen Code und geben Sie dann Ihre Kontoinformationen ein.

Kontoinhaber

Kontonummer

IBAN

BIC

Bestätigen

Bestätigen

CLOSE

Please enable JavaScript in your browser to complete this form.

1Konto

2Benutzerdaten

3Bankdatan

Vorname

Nachname

GeburtsdatumMM123456789101112/DD12345678910111213141516171819202122232425262728293031/YYYY202420232022202120202019201820172016201520142013201220112010200920082007200620052004200320022001200019991998199719961995199419931992199119901989198819871986198519841983198219811980197919781977197619751974197319721971197019691968196719661965196419631962196119601959195819571956195519541953195219511950194919481947194619451944194319421941194019391938193719361935193419331932193119301929192819271926192519241923192219211920

Adresse

Postleitzahl

Bestätigen

E-Mail-Adresse \*

Passwort \*

* Mind. 8 Zeichen
* Großbuchstaben
* Kleinbuchstaben
* Zahlen

Handynummer (Optional)

BisherigeBestätigen

Bitte geben Sie unten Ihre Bankdaten ein. Um Sie zu authentifizieren, leisten wir eine kleine Einzahlung mit einem eindeutigen Referenzcode auf Ihr Bankkonto. Bitte überprüfen Sie Ihre Bank auf diesen Code und geben Sie dann Ihre Kontoinformationen ein.

Kontoinhaber

Kontonummer

IBAN

BIC

Bestätigen

Bestätigen

×

Please enable JavaScript in your browser to complete this form.

Es wurde eine Einzahlung mit einem eindeutigen Referenzcode auf Ihr Bankkonto vorgenommen. Um Ihre Identität zu bestätigen, geben Sie bitte den Code in das Feld unten ein, um Ihre Bankdaten zu überprüfen.

CODE\*\*\*\*\*-\*\*\*\*\*\*\*\*

Bestätigen

×
